MOHAMMED ALI HACHICHA

Software Developer

+216 24 077 446

♥ Tunisia, Sfax

@ dalyhachicha7@gmail.com

@ daly-hachicha.webflow.io

SUMMARY

Having a passion for computers has led me to expand my knowledge in computer science from a young age. I was absolutely attracted to computer software and games which later developed into an interest in programming.

I am mostly self-taught, as well as having a fundamental license degree in computer science from the Higher Institute of Computer Science of Mahdia.

I also have some experience developing mobile and web applications as a freelancer.

SKILLS

Machine Learning & Al		Computer Vision	SQL	
MongoDB	Firebase	Mobile developme	nt (Flutter)	
Flask Data Structure and Algorithms				

EXPERIENCE

Python Developer

Freelance

🛗 2019 - Ongoing

- Modified existing software to correct coding errors, upgrade and improve overall performance
- Implimented simple machine learning algorithms (Linear Regression, Decision tree,Random forest)
- Implimented inceptionV3 model for face shape classification (end of studies project)
- Implimented OpenCV and mediapipe for extracting face landmarks (end of studies project)

Flutter Developer

Freelance

2021 - Ongoing

- Modified existing projects to correct coding errors, upgrade and improve overall performance
- Implementation of Firebase
- Design and developed 2 apps
- Integration/Widget/Unit Testing

PROGRAMMING

Python Proficient	••••
Dart Advanced	••••
JavaScript Advanced	••••
HTML/CSS Intermediate	••••
SQL Intermediate	••••

STRENGTHS



Calculus 1 & 2

Committed to lifelong Learning

EDUCATION

Fundamental License in Computer Science

Higher Institue of Computer Science - Mahdia

10/2018 - 07/2021